<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Kelsey Pawelek</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Kelsey Pawelek</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 22:55:05 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Dec 2020 22:55:05 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>BEWARE OF R and Snakes</title>
      <link>/post/1/01/01/python-an-interesting-learn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/1/01/01/python-an-interesting-learn/</guid>
      <description>R=Studio? &amp;amp; Python=Snakes? These two languages are very interesting--
As we have previously learned in SDS 348, R and Python have some differences.
For instance, R syntax is fat (sorry buddy) and python syntax looks soooo clean! Both hey they are both still kinda confusing but SO fun to learn!
For the majority of this semester, we have explored the R Studio world.
Here is R Studio at work: library(reticulate) hehe &amp;lt;- &amp;quot;good, how are you, buddy?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kelsey Pawelek&#39;s Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>Kelsey Danielle Pawelek 361-701-1101 kelseypawelek@yahoo.com
  Address P O Box 1324 Orange Grove, TX 78372
5811 Mesa Drive Apt # 531 Austin, TX 78731
 CAREER OBJECTIVE Accomplished, hardworking student earning a Bachelor’s degree in Biology from University of Texas at Austin. Aiming to attend Physician’s Assistant Medical School after graduation. Currently getting certified by the National Healthcareer Association as a Certified Clinical Medical Assistant.
 EDUCATION The University of Texas at Austin Bachelor of Science and Art (BSA) Biology Minor in Health Communications Pre-Physician’s Assistant Expected Graduation: December 2020 GPA: 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2:Modeling, Testing, and Predicting- Traumatic Brain Injuries from 2014</title>
      <link>/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project2/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: Traumatic Brain Injury The dataset titled &#39;tbi_age&#39; contains information on traumatic brain injuries with five different variables (age_group, type, injury_mechanism, number_est, and rate_est). A traumatic brain injury is caused by an external force exerted onto the head or other body parts which end up causing trauma to the brain in some way. Within this dataset, the following variables are recorded: the age group, the type of care received/occurrence whether it was an emergency visit, hospitalization, or resulted in death, how the injury occurred (example: fall, assault, self-harm, etc), the estimated observed cases in 2014, and the rate per 100,000 cases in 2014.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project1: Do Food Consumption and Drink Consumption affect CO2 Emissions in Countries around the World? </title>
      <link>/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project1/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this analysis, the datasets &amp;quot;food_consumption&amp;quot; and &amp;quot;drinks&amp;quot; are examined to determine potenital relationships, summary statistics, and visual analyses. The dataset &amp;quot;food_consumption&amp;quot; contains data from the Food and Agriculture Organization of the United Nations documenting data on countries around the world, specific food categories, the consumption of these foods (kg/person/year), and lastly, the CO2 emission (kg CO2/person/year). The dataset &amp;quot;drinks&amp;quot; contains data from the World Health Organization and Global Information System on Alcohol and Health which contains data on countries around the world, beer servings (per person), spirit servings (per person), wine servings (per person), and the total liters of alcohol consumed by a person.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
